A Guide to the Governor Timothy M. Kaine, Policy Office, Records, 2002-2010 (bulk 2006-2009)
Library of Virginia
- II. Regulations, 2003-2010 (accession 44690)., Extent: 14.70 cubic feet (42 boxes). (Box 7-48)
  - TRANSPORTATION, Secretary of
    - Department of Motor Vehicles
      - Hauling Permit Regulation, New Regulation to Establish Requirements for Issuance of Permits to Haul Overweight and over Dimension Vehicles over Highways of Virginia: 24 VAC 20-81, 1675/4988 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Department of Transportation
      - Land Use Permit Manual, Repeal and Replace Existing Regulation (24 VAC 30-150-10) with Updated and Rewritten Regulation Under Same Title and New Number (24 VAC 30-151-10 et seq.): 24 VAC 30-151 and 150, 769/3107 (Box 46, Folder 5)
      - Commonwealth Transportation Board, Access Management Regulations, Minor Arterials, Collectors and Local Streets, Promulgation of APA-Subject Regulation and Related Standards to Satisfy Legislative Mandate: 24 VAC 30-73, 2692/4674 (Box 46, Folder 6)
      - Access Management Regulations, Minor Arterials, Collectors and Local Streets, Promulgation of APA-Subject Regulation and Related Standards to Satisfy Legislative Mandate: 24 VAC 30-73, 2692/5140 (Box 46, Folder 7)
      - Commonwealth Transportation Board, Traffic Impact Analysis Regulations, Area Plan Streamlined Analysis: 24 VAC 30-155, 3183/5363 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Motor Vehicle Dealer Board
      - Motor Vehicle Dealer Fees, Fee Increase: 24 VAC 22-20, 2164/3913 (Box 46, Folder 9)
      - Motor Vehicle Dealer Fees, Fee Increase: 24 VAC 22-20, 2164/3811 (Box 46, Folder 10)
      - Motor Vehicle Dealer Board, Fee Increase: 24 VAC 22-20, 2164/4205 (Box 46, Folder 11)
      - Establish Regulations for Mandatory, Continuing Education for Independent (Used) Motor Vehicle Dealers: 24 VAC 22-40, 2605/4534 (Box 46, Folder 12)
      - Independent Motor Vehicle Dealer Dealer-Operator Recertification Regulations, Establish Regulations for Mandatory, Continuing Education for Independent (Used) Motor Vehicle Dealers: 24 VAC 22-40, 2605/5162 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous Regulations, 2009-2010
    - Secretary of Natural Resources, Dept. of Conservation and Recreation, Amend Parts I, II and III of the Virginia Stormwater Management Program Permit Regulations to Address Water Quality and Quantity and Local Stormwater Management Program Criteria: 4 VAC 50-60, 1916/5397 (Box 46, Folder 14)
    - Secretary of Natural Resources, Dept. of Conservation and Recreation, Stormwater Management Regulation, Establish Water Quality Criteria for New Development Activities with the Chesapeake Bay Watershed: 4 VAC 50-60, 3199/5398 (Box 46, Folder 15)
    - Secretary of Natural Resources, Dept. of Conservation and Recreation, Stormwater Management Regulations, Amendments to Statewide Permit Fee Schedule to Improve the Administration and Implementation of Fees: 4 VAC 50-60, 1915/5396 (Box 46, Folder 16)
    - Secretary of Commerce and Trade, Dept. of Housing and Community Development, Update and Amend Enterprise Zone Grant Program Regulations: 13 VAC 5-112, 3160/5323 (Box 46, Folder 17)
    - Secretary of Education, Dept. of Education, Vocation Education Regulations, Revisions to Reflect Changes in Federal and State Laws, Eliminate Any Duplication: 8 VAC 20-120, 3187/5369 (Box 46, Folder 18)
    - Secretary of Natural Resources, Dept. of Environmental Quality, Plasticulture Operations Regulation, Initial Adoption: 9 VAC 25-870, 3178/5357 (Box 46, Folder 19)
    - Secretary of Education, Dept. of Education, Regulations Governing Local School Boards and School Divisions, Incorporate Provisions on Fees and Charges as New Section of 8 VAC 20-720: 8 VAC 20-720, 2719/5279 (Box 46, Folder 20)
    - Secretary of Education, Dept. of Education, Regulations Governing Local School Boards and School Divisions, Incorporate Textbook Provisions into Consolidated Regulations: 8 VAC 20-720, 2669/5315 (Box 46, Folder 21)
    - Secretary of Agriculture and Forestry, Dept. of Agriculture and Consumer Services, Health Requirements Governing the Control of Equine Infectious Anemia in Virginia, Repeals the Alternate Testing Requirements for Horses Assembled for Sale or Auction in Virginia: 2 VAC 5-70, 2464/5253 (Box 46, Folder 22)
    - Secretary of Health and Human Resources, Dept. of Social Services, Food Stamp Program, Restructure and Rename Program to Supplemental Nutrition Assistance Program: 22 VAC 40-601, 2978/5218 (Box 46, Folder 23)
    - Fast-Track Regulation Approval Sheets, 2007 (Box 46, Folder 24)
    - Emergency Extensions Approved, 2008-2009 (Box 46, Folder 25)
    - Secretary of Public Safety, Dept. of Juvenile Justice, Regulation Governing Juvenile Secure Detention Centers, Combines in Single Document Provisions Applicable to Juvenile Secure Detention Centers: 6 VAC 35-101, 2973/5299 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Secretary of Health and Human Resources, DMHMRSAS, General Revisions to Clarify, Update, Simplify and Align with Current Code Provisions: 12 VAC 35-105, 2288/4901 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Secretary of Commerce and Trade, Department of Professional and Occupational Regulation, Regulations Governing Polygraph Examiners, General Review 2009: 18 VAC 120-30, 3177/5355 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Secretary of Health and Human Resources, VDH, Waterworks Regulation, Chronically Noncompliant Waterworks: 12 VAC 5-590, 2743/5229 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Secretary of Natural Resources, DEQ, Air Pollution Control Board, Permits for Stationary Sources, Permits for New and Modified Sources (Rev. H05): 9 VAC 5-80, 1896/5073 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Secretary of Health and Human Resources, DMAS, Board of Medical Assistance Services, Waivered Services, MCO Rural Exception: 12 VAC 30-120, 3147/5303 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Secretary of Natural Resources, Dept. of Conservation and Recreation, Virginia State Parks Regulations, Amend and Clarify the State Park Regulations: 4 VAC 5-30, 3170/5342 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Secretary of Health and Human Resources, DMAS, Amount, Duration and Scope of Medical and Remedial Care and Services, Prior Authorization of Intensive In-Home Services: 12 VAC 30-50, 2653/5280 (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Secretary of Health and Human Resources, VDH, Regulations for the Immunization of School Children, Update of the Regulations: 12 VAC 5-110, 2593/5322 (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Secretary of Health and Human Resources, DMAS, Methods and Standards for Establishing Payment Rate, Other Types of Care, Ambulatory Surgery Center and Outpatient Rehabilitation Facility Reimbursement: 12 VAC 30-80, 2690/5345 (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Secretary of Commerce and Trade, DPOR, Common Interest Community Board, Common Interest Community Manager Regulations: 18 VAC 48-50, 2799/5354 (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - Secretary of Health and Human Resources, DHP, Regulations for Licensure of Occupational Therapists, Licensure of Occupational Therapy Assistants: 18 VAC 85-80, 2758/5356 (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - Secretary of Public Safety, ABC, Amendments to Advertising and Tied-House Regulations to Conform to Recent General Assembly Action and to Simplify and Update them: 3 VAC 5-20, 2456/5333 (Box 47, Folder 13)
    - Secretary of Education, DOE, Regulations Governing Educational Services for Gifted Students, Revision of Regulations School Divisions Must Meet in their Gifted Education Programs, K-12: 8 VAC 20-40, 1933/5074 (Box 47, Folder 14)
    - Secretary of Agriculture and Forestry, DOF, Virginia State Forest Regulations, Amend Requirements for Carrying Handguns in State Forests: 4 VAC 10-30, 2980/5277 (Box 47, Folder 15)
    - Secretary of Commerce and Trade, DMME, Geothermal Energy Regulations, Amendments Regarding the Regulation of Geothermal Energy: 4 VAC 25-170, 2646/5011 (Box 47, Folder 16)
    - Secretary of Health and Human Resources, VDH, Regulations Governing the State Dental Scholarship Program, Amend Regulations Following Periodic Review: 12 VAC 5-520, 2624/5149 (Box 47, Folder 17)
    - Secretary of Public Safety, DJJ, Regulation Governing Juvenile Correctional Centers, Comprehensive Review and Consolidation of Regulations Applicable to Juvenile Correctional Centers: 6 VAC 35-71, 2976/5298 (Box 47, Folder 18)
    - Secretary of Public Safety, DCJS, Regulations Relating to Private Security Services, Comprehensive Review: 6 VAC 20-171, 2725/5242 (Box 47, Folder 19)
    - Secretary of Commerce and Trade, DPOR, Board for Contractors Regulations, Fee Adjustment to Comply Section 54.1-113 of the Code of Virginia (Callahan Act): 18 VAC 50-22, 2589/5177 (Box 47, Folder 20)
    - Secretary of Commerce and Trade, DPOR,Individual License and Certification Regulations, Fee Adjustment to Comply with Section 54.1-113 of the Code of Virginia (Callahan Act): 18 VAC 50-30, 2590/5178 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Secretary of Health and Human Resources, VDH, Regulations Governing the Virginia Physician Loan Repayment Program, Adoption of Regulations to Administer a Loan Repayment Program: 12 VAC 5-508, 716/4007 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Secretary of Public Safety, DJJ, Regulation Governing Juvenile Group Homes and Halfway Houses, Combines in Single Document Provisions Applicable to Juvenile Group Homes and Halfway Houses: 6 VAC 35-41, 2974/5311 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Secretary of Administration, DHRM, Commonwealth of Virginia Health Benefits Program, This Action will Amend Section 1 VAC 55 320(E) to Include Adults, Other than Spouses and Incapacitated Adult Children, as Participants in the Health Benefits Plan for State Employees: 1 VAC 55-320, 3182/5401 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Secretary of Natural Resources, Air Pollution Control Board, Consumer and Commercial Products Regulation (REV 06): 9 VAC 5-45, 2328/5373 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Secretary of Health and Human Resources, DSS, Auxiliary Grants Program: 22 VAC 40-25, 2652/5054 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Secretary of Health and Human Resources, DHP, Regulations of the Virginia Board of Optometry, Standards of Conduct: 18 VAC 105-20, 2538/5381 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Secretary of Transportation, VDOT, Commonwealth Transportation Board, Land Use Permit Regulations: 24 VAC 30-150-10, 769/5228 (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - Secretary of Health and Human Resources, DHP, Virginia Board of Pharmacy, Standards of Conduct: 18 VAC 110-20, 2585/5406 (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - Secretary of Health and Human Resources, DHP, Virginia Board of Optometry, Continuing Education Requirements: 18 VAC 105-20, 2048/5382 (Box 48, Folder 12)
- III. Legislative Files, 2006-2009 (accession 44701)., Extent: 33.60 cubic feet (96 boxes). (Box 49-141, 170-172)
  The Legislative Files series is housed in 96 boxes and is arranged chronologically by legislative session. This series documents the Governor's Policy Office review of all legislation introduced by the General Assembly during the Kaine administration. Each file usually contains the text of each bill including any amendments, bill tracking information, Governor's Summaries (prepared by the Division of Legislative Services), Legislative Action Summaries (for bills tabled, withdrawn or killed in committee), Governor's Policy Office Enrolled Bill Review Forms, Enrolled Bill Reviews (by Cabinet Secretary), Department of Planning and Budget Fiscal Impact Statements, Attorney General's Recommendations to the Governor (restricted for 75 years - attorney/client privilege) and other miscellaneous legislation-related documents which explain in detail various bills brought before and voted upon by the General Assembly. In addition to providing the policy positions and decisions of the Kaine administration, the Legislative Files may also be useful to researchers in determining legislative intent.
  Each Governor's Summary prepared by the Division of Legislative Services contains the bill number, patron, bill summary, other information and name of reviewer. The Enrolled Bill Reviews, prepared by the agency most affected by the legislation, summarize the bill and the number of votes for passage achieved by the House and Senate. The reviews include affected constituents' summary, agency analysis and recommendations, recommendations by the appropriate cabinet secretary and notations as to whether the Governor should sign, ask to amend or veto the bill. The Governor's Policy Office Enrolled Bill Review Form contains the vote in the House and Senate, a list and explanation of any no votes, fiscal impact (if any), summary of bill and comments by a Policy Office analyst (Mark Rubin, Maribel Ramos, Felix Sarfo-Kantanka, Jennie Moline, Suzette Denslow, Steven Gould, William L. Murray, Wayne Turnage), and recommendations to Governor Warner from the Analyst, Director of Policy (Brian Sheppard), Counselor (Lawrence Roberts, 2006-2009 and Mark Rubin, 2009-2010) and Chief of Staff (William H. Leighty, 2006-2007 and Wayne Turnage, 2007-2010) if the Governor should sign, veto or amend the bill. Some files contain Department of Planning and Budget fiscal impact statements which detail the monetary affect any legislation might have on the budget. The Office of the Attorney General's Recommendations to the Governor contain check boxes noting if the legislation conflicts with existing law or the Virginia and Federal constitutions, as well as any suggested amendments or comments. The Attorney General's Recommendations are restricted due to attorney-client privilege. Other files also contain correspondence including e-mail messages from bill supporters and opponents related to that particular bill. Also included in this series are Legislative Action Summaries that contain agency and cabinet secretary recommendations and handwritten comments and Governor's suggested amendments and veto messages.
  The Division of Legislative Services website provides the status of individual bills and related information from the 1994 session to the present.
  - 2006 Regular Session
    - House of Delegates
      - HB 1 (06) Highways, Adjustment of Claims Resulting from Certain Contracts, signed 23 March 2006 (Box 49, Folder 1)
      - HB 2 (06) Richmond-Petersburg Turnpike Authority; Elizabeth River Tunnel Commission, signed 24 March 2006 (Box 49, Folder 2)
      - HB 5 (06) Trout Fishing; Department of Game and Inland Fisheries to Issue Special Permits for Handicapped, signed 23 February 2006 (Box 49, Folder 3)
      - HB 13 (06) Tuberculosis; Establishing Library of Isolates for Purpose of Disease Strain Analysis, signed 7 March 2006 (Box 49, Folder 4)
      - HB 15 (06) Workforce Transition Act; Restricts Severance Benefits for Certain State Employees, signed 6 April 2006 (Box 49, Folder 5)
      - HB 19 (06) Standards of Quality; Calculation of High School Graduation Rates, signed 5 April 2006 (Box 49, Folder 6)
      - HB 20 (06) Scholastic Records; Electronic Storage thereof, signed 7 March 2006 (Box 49, Folder 7)
      - HB 21 (06) Victims of Crime; Notice of Court Hearings, signed 30 March 2006 (Box 49, Folder 8)
      - HB 22 (06) Motor Vehicle Safety Inspections; Increase in Fees, signed 5 April 2006 (Box 49, Folder 9)
      - HB 24 (06) Absentee Ballot; Assistance to Persons Voting, Penalties, signed 30 March 2006 (Box 49, Folder 10)
      - HB 25 (06) Law-Enforcement Officer; May Detain Person for Suspicious Behavior, signed 31 March 2006 (Box 49, Folder 11)
      - HB 33 (06) State Employees; Military Leave of Absence, signed 5 April 2006 (Box 49, Folder 12)
      - HB 36 (06) Higher Educational Institutions; Violations of Chapter on Regulations thereof, Penalty, signed 7 March 2006 (Box 49, Folder 13)
      - HB 37 (06) Retirement System; Benefits for Emergency Medical Technicians, signed 31 March 2006 (Box 49, Folder 14)
      - HB 38 (06) Vocational Schools, Out-of-State; Accreditation of those Operating within State, signed 6 April 2006 (Box 49, Folder 15)
      - HB 41 (06) Driving under Influence of Alcohol; Penalty for Subsequent Offense, signed 23 March 2006 (Box 49, Folder 16)
      - HB 45 (06) Death Penalty; Restricted for those 18 Years or Older at Time of Offense, signed 6 March 2006 (Box 49, Folder 17)
      - HB 47 (06) Douthat State Park; Pilot Program Repealed, signed 14 February 2006 (Box 49, Folder 18)
      - HB 48 (06) CHAMPS Program; Coordinated Medical Care in City of Chesapeake, signed 7 March 2006 (Box 49, Folder 19)
      - HB 49 (06) Scholars Program; Provisions Relating thereto, signed 7 March 2006 (Box 49, Folder 20)
      - HB 50 (06) Work-Study Program; Provisions Relating thereto, signed 7 March 2006 (Box 49, Folder 21)
      - HB 56 (06) Child Abuse or Neglect; Mandatory Reporting by Eligibility Workers; Penalty,signed 4 April 2006 (Box 49, Folder 22)
      - HB 57 (06) Community College System; Articulation Agreements and Transferable Credits, signed 4 April 2006 (Box 49, Folder 23)
      - HB 58 (06) Computers; School Resource Officers to Provide Internet Safety Instruction to Students, signed 7 March 2006 (Box 49, Folder 24)
      - HB 59 (06) Health Insurance; Credits for Retired State Employees, signed 5 April 2006 (Box 49, Folder 25)
      - HB 61 (06) Voter Registration; Duties of State Board of Election, signed 30 March 2006 (Box 49, Folder 26)
      - HB 62 (06) Judges; Increases Number in General District Court, signed 3 March 2006 (Box 49, Folder 27)
      - HB 63 (06) Judges; Increases Number in Circuit Court, signed 3 March 2006 (Box 49, Folder 28)
      - HB 64 (06) Public Procurement Act; Bids or Proposals for Transportation-Related Projects, amended 10 April 2006 (Box 49, Folder 29)
      - HB 65 (06) Unemployment Compensation, Commission on; Repeals Sunset Provision, signed 31 March 2006 (Box 49, Folder 30)
      - HB 68 (06) Courts Technology Fund; Created, Increase in Certain Fees, signed 5 April 2006 (Box 49, Folder 31)
      - HB 69 (06) Retail Sales and Use Tax; Exemptions Include Medicines for Commercial Farm Animals, signed 30 March 2006 (Box 49, Folder 32)
      - HB 70 (06) Assault and Battery; School Bus Drivers, Penalty, amended 10 April 2006 (Box 49, Folder 33)
      - HB 71 (06) Elections; Certification of Political Party Candidates for General, Special and Primary, signed 23 March 2006 (Box 49, Folder 34)
      - HB 73 (06) Social Services; City Council Member Appointed to Local Board, signed 23 March 2006 (Box 49, Folder 35)
      - HB 77 (06) Higher Educational Institutions Bond Act of 2006; Created, signed 4 April 2006 (Box 49, Folder 36)
      - HB 78 (06) Zoning Ordinance; Reconstruction/Restoration of Involuntarily Damaged or Destroyed Nonconformities, signed 30 March 2006 (Box 49, Folder 37)
      - HB 83 (06) Public Building Authority; Issuance of Bonds for State Agency Radio System for State Police, signed 30 March 2006 (Box 49, Folder 38)
      - HB 90 (06) Driver's Licenses; Extension of Expiration for Military Personnel or Member of Diplomatic Service, signed 23 March 2006 (Box 49, Folder 39)
      - HB 93 (06) Environmental Site Assessments; Local Government to Adopt Ordinances Requiring, signed 4 April 2006 (Box 49, Folder 40)
      - HB 95 (06) Student, New; Certain Information Required Upon Registration to Public School, signed 7 March 2006 (Box 49, Folder 41)
      - HB 101 (06) Constitutional Amendment; Marriage May Exist Only Between a Man and Woman, amended 8 March 2006 (Box 49, Folder 42)
      - HB 102 (06) Driver's License; Operating Vehicle with Suspended or Revoked License, Penalty, signed 31 March 2006 (Box 49, Folder 43)
      - HB 104 (06) Meherrin River; Portion in Brunswick County Designated as State Scenic River, signed 14 February 2006 (Box 49, Folder 44)
      - HB 105 (06) Political Campaign Advertisements; Disclosure Requirements therefor, Definitions, signed 6 April 2006 (Box 49, Folder 45)
      - HB 106 (06) Warning Lights; Use of Red or Red and White Lights by NASA's Wallops Flight Facility Vehicles, signed 23 March 2006 (Box 49, Folder 46)
      - HB 110 (06) Aging Population; State Agencies to Prepare Strategic Plan on Impact thereof, Report, signed 7 March 2006 (Box 49, Folder 47)
      - HB 111 (06) All-Terrain Vehicles; Allows Local Governments in Northern Virginia to Prohibit Operation thereof, amended 10 April 2006 (Box 49, Folder 48)
      - HB 113 (06) Alcoholic Beverages; Penalty for Purchasing for Certain Persons, signed 23 March 2006 (Box 49, Folder 49)
      - HB 115 (06) Garnishment Forms and Summonses; Requires Clarity in Language therein, signed 7 March 2006 (Box 49, Folder 50)
      - HB 121 (06) Real Estate Tax; Increases Amount of Exemptions for Elderly or Disabled in Northern Virginia, singed 5 April 2006 (Box 50, Folder 1)
      - HB 122 (06) SWAM Businesses; Additional Certification Not Required to Participate in any Program, amended 10 April 2006 (Box 50, Folder 2)
      - HB 125 (06) Conservators of the Peace; Includes NASA's Special Agents and Security Police Officers, signed 23 March 2006 (Box 50, Folder 3)
      - HB 126 (06) Juvenile Detention Hearings; Judge May Designate Courthouse Where to be Held, signed 23 March 2006 (Box 50, Folder 4)
      - HB 127 (06) Court-Appointed Counsel; Written Request for Compensation, signed 30 March 2006 (Box 50, Folder 5)
      - HB 128 (06) Condominium Act; Authorizing Condominium Association to be Applicants in Land Use Matters, signed 23 February 2006 (Box 50, Folder 6)
      - HB 132 (06) Eminent Domain; Jury to Determine Just Compensation, signed 5 April 2006 (Box 50, Folder 7)
      - HB 134 (06) Higher Educational Institutions; to Report Assignment of any Intellectual Property Interests, amended 11 March 2006 (Box 50, Folder 8)
      - HB 138 (06) Voter Registration; Spouse or Dependent of Military Member, Exceptions, signed 31 March 2006 (Box 50, Folder 9)
      - HB 141 (06) Impact Fees for Transportation; Authorize Fauquier and Spotsylvania Counties to Impose, amended 10 April 2006 (Box 50, Folder 10)
      - HB 143 (06) Highways, Bridges and Interchanges; Allows Transportation Board to Name, amended 10 April 2006 (Box 50, Folder 11)
      - HB 147 (06) Service Districts; Localities May Contribute from General Fund for Certain Government Services, signed 23 February 2006 (Box 50, Folder 12)
      - HB 148 (06) Stormwater Management Program; Includes Enlargement, Improvement and Maintenance of Dams, signed 23 February 2006 (Box 50, Folder 13)
      - HB 151 (06) Resident Trainee; Name Changed to Funeral Service Interns, signed 7 March 2006 (Box 50, Folder 14)
      - HB 153 (06) Halal Food; Regulation of Sale, Penalty, signed 31 March 2006 (Box 50, Folder 15)
      - HB 168 (06) Income Tax, State; False Claims of Employment Status, Penalty, signed 31 March 2006 (Box 50, Folder 16)
      - HB 170 (06) Voter Registration; DMV to Furnish List of Non-Citizens to Board of Elections, amended 10 April 2006 (Box 50, Folder 17)
      - HB 172 (06) Wildlife Diseases; Control thereof, signed 23 February 2006 (Box 50, Folder 18)
      - HB 175 (06) Overweight Farm Vehicles; May Operate at Extended Weights Authorized, signed 4 April 2006 (Box 50, Folder 19)
      - HB 193 (06) Deposit Accounts and Certificates of Deposit; Statute of Limitations, signed 5 April 2006 (Box 50, Folder 20)
      - HB 194 (06) Real Estate; Special Commissioner to Sell Property, etc., to Make Tax Sales Less Costly, signed 30 March 2006 (Box 50, Folder 21)
      - HB 195 (06) Industrial Loan Companies; Certain Provisions for those Out-of-State, signed 6 April 2006 (Box 50, Folder 22)
      - HB 201 (06) Toll Facilities; Localities May Have Agreements for Construction and Operation thereof (Box 50, Folder 23)
      - HB 203 (06) Boy Scouts of America and Girl Scouts of the USA; Equal Access to Public Facilities, signed 7 March 2006 (Box 50, Folder 24)
      - HB 206 (06) Road Construction; Expands Powers of Service Districts to Include, signed 31 March 2006 (Box 50, Folder 25)
      - HB 207 (06) Correctional Facilities, Community-Based; Location and Notice, signed 24 March 2006 (Box 50, Folder 26)